(Steph:)Leonard? Why haven't I heard a thing about
this woman who lives across the hall...
(Steph:)...and comes into your apartment
in the morning in her underwear?
Um. Uh...
(Leonard:)She's heard about you
because we're, you know, involved...
(Leonard:)...and you haven't heard about her
because...
(Leonard:)I never slept with her, I swear.
In Leonard's defense,
it wasn't for lack of trying.
- Thank you, Sheldon.
- You're welcome, Leonard.
(Leonard:)Look, I'm just saying, um...
...Penny is one of our many neighbors,
you know.
(Leonard:)And in our building,
neighbors come and go.
Well, it's very casual. No dress code or...
Some mornings, I'll mosey down
to the third floor in my pajamas...
(Leonard:)...and have cereal with Mrs. Vartabedian.
Really? I've never once been invited
to have cereal with Mrs. Vartabedian.